<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AWS Direct Connect on Internship Report</title><link>https://khongphuongpro0.github.io/workshopSocial/categories/aws-direct-connect/</link><description>Recent content in AWS Direct Connect on Internship Report</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khongphuongpro0.github.io/workshopSocial/categories/aws-direct-connect/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog 2. Building Enterprise-Ready Hybrid Network Connectivity on AWS for SAP Cloud ERP Private (formerly known as RISE with SAP)</title><link>https://khongphuongpro0.github.io/workshopSocial/3-blogstranslated/3.2-blog2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongphuongpro0.github.io/workshopSocial/3-blogstranslated/3.2-blog2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Are you ready to unlock the full potential of your SAP workloads on AWS? Let’s solve one of the most crucial pieces of the puzzle: establishing secure, reliable network connectivity between your company networks and your cloud ERP workloads.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At AWS, as we’ve helped customers implement their &lt;strong>SAP Cloud ERP Private&lt;/strong> workloads (formerly known as RISE with SAP), three questions understandably emerge:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>“How do we establish secure connections to our private cloud ERP environments?”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“What’s the most cost-effective network architecture for our use case?”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“Should we implement &lt;strong>Direct Connect, Site-to-Site VPN&lt;/strong>, or both?”&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Network connectivity decisions made today will impact your SAP operations for years to come, affecting everything from system performance to disaster recovery capabilities. In this guide, we’ll cut through the complexity and show you how to connect your existing infrastructure to AWS for SAP Cloud ERP Private.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>